[
  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Accelerando stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Gradually getting slower",
      "Stay the same speed",
      "Stop playing"
    ],
    "correct": "Gradually getting quicker"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Adagio stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Gradually getting slower",
      "Gradually getting quicker",
      "Fast"
    ],
    "correct": "Slow"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Allegretto stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Gradually getting slower",
      "Gradually getting quicker",
      "Slow"
    ],
    "correct": "Fairly quick"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Allegro stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Very slow",
      "Very Fast",
      "Slow"
    ],
    "correct": "Quick"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Andante stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Very loud",
      "Fast Speed",
      "Slow Speed"
    ],
    "correct": "Medium Speed"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Lento stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Very loud",
      "Fast Speed",
      "Very quiet"
    ],
    "correct": "Slow"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Rallentando stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Very loud",
      "Stay the same speed",
      "Gradually getting quicker"
    ],
    "correct": "Gradually getting slower"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Ritardando stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Very loud",
      "Stay the same speed",
      "Gradually getting quicker"
    ],
    "correct": "Gradually getting slower"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Ritenuto stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Immediately quicker",
      "Stay the same speed",
      "Gradually getting quicker"
    ],
    "correct": "Immediately slower"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Tempo stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Space/Time",
      "Speed/Space",
      "Slow Pace"
    ],
    "correct": "Speed/Time"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Piano stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Very Loud",
      "Loud",
      "Very Quiet"
    ],
    "correct": "Quiet"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Pianissimo stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Very Loud",
      "Loud",
      "Quiet"
    ],
    "correct": "Very Quiet"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Mezzo Piano stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Very Loud",
      "Quiet",
      "Very Quiet"
    ],
    "correct": "Moderately Quiet"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Forte stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Very Loud",
      "Moderately Loud",
      "Quiet"
    ],
    "correct": "Loud"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Fortissimo stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Loud",
      "Moderately Loud",
      "Quiet"
    ],
    "correct": "Very Loud"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Mezzo Forte stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Very Loud",
      "Loud",
      "Quiet"
    ],
    "correct": "Moderately Loud"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Crescendo stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Quiet",
      "Loud",
      "Gradually getting quieter"
    ],
    "correct": "Gradually getting louder"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Diminuendo stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Quiet",
      "Loud",
      "Gradually getting louder"
    ],
    "correct": "Gradually getting quieter"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Decrescendo stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Quiet",
      "Loud",
      "Gradually getting louder"
    ],
    "correct": "Gradually getting quieter"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Cantabile stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "In a sudden style",
      "In a quick style",
      "In a shouting style"
    ],
    "correct": "In a singing style"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Da Capo stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Repeat from the sign",
      "Repeat from the end",
      "In a shouting style"
    ],
    "correct": "Repeat from the beginning"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Dal Segno stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Repeat from the beginning",
      "Repeat from the end",
      "In a shouting style"
    ],
    "correct": "Repeat from the sign"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Fine stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "The beginning",
      "The chorus",
      "The middle"
    ],
    "correct": "The end"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Legato stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Disjointed",
      "Broken",
      "Roughly"
    ],
    "correct": "Smoothly"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Moderato stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Disjointed",
      "Broken",
      "Brief"
    ],
    "correct": "Moderately"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Poco stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "A lot",
      "Moderately",
      "Pointed"
    ],
    "correct": "A little"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does 8va stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "The 8th note",
      "Same Octave",
      "Octave Below"
    ],
    "correct": "Octave Above"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does 8vb stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "The 8th note",
      "Same Octave",
      "Octave Above"
    ],
    "correct": "Octave Below"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Accent stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Detached",
      "Change pace",
      "Emphasise nothing"
    ],
    "correct": "Emphasise the note"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "What does Staccato stand for?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Attached",
      "Change pace",
      "Emphasise nothing"
    ],
    "correct": "Detached"
  },

  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "How do you draw an Accent?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Shown with a square above or below the note head",
      "Shown with a triangle above or below the note head",
      "Shown with a dot above or below the note head"
    ],
    "correct": "Shown with a > above or below the note head"
  },
  
  {
    "grade": 1,
    "category": "terms",
    "question": "How do you draw Staccato?",
    "incorrect": [
      "Shown with a square above or below the note head",
      "Shown with a triangle above or below the note head",
      "Shown with a > above or below the note head"
    ],
    "correct": "Shown with a dot above or below the note head"
  }
]
